Tanaka, because she didn't manage to convert the one in the first half.
Chante for Brazil and they've won it!
Wow, late on!
The substitute!
I'll tell you what, Rafael is technically a bulletin if you put that in the back of the net.
I would not!
Macintosh teaches a master class in the 400m as she masters the field to win her first
Olympic gold medal.
It is Katie Grimes with the silver and America gets the bronze as well in the form of Emma
Great Britain and the Netherlands a coat of paint apart it's going to come down to that
Great Britain and the Netherlands who is it oh it's the Netherlands
Great Britain wins silver New Zealand take the bronze
Yeah they're trying to keep chair to the back of the court and she comes
She's gonna be tough to catch but watch ball in third place she has performed super superhuman
Feats a world record indoors over 400 meters this winter just gone USA leading but here comes ball
Is she gonna get there is she gonna run out of track no she's not it's good well it is fast
Once again as she tends to speed up and she goes look at the difference between these two
That's unbelievable
As people i'm almost yeah i always can't speak she's almost close to getting
Touch oh yes there is the header that was on purpose
So
The olympic champion can he become quite frankly
An icon let's see if he can do it can he hold it together he's on his phone
Oh that's better it's huge it's a great throw and it will surely be a new olympic record
No option but to pull it level but look at labration he pulls himself level on the track
But has he got the acceleration to come round it comes now into the finishing straight
Labration is the olympic champion for a second time running you knew it was coming you saw the
Acceleration he is now they do need the miracle shot joanna pushes it forward williams gets it
Today over the line that is how fine the margins are
Moorgard started strong capturing the first game with a display of skill and
Unpredictability that left the crowd buzzing about another potential upset